Guide to the William T. Grant Foundation records FA004
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Grant files, 1940-1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; 3; Tavistock Institute of Human Relations; Spock, Benjamin (1903-1998); Freud, Anna (1895-1982); Hampstead Child-Therapy Clinic; Goodall, Jane (1934); 96.9 Cubic Feet 246 letter document boxes, 5 legal document boxes, 4 half-legal boxes, 1 card f
  - Grant files, 1940s - 1990s, bulk 1970-1985; 1970-1985; A
    - Montreal Children's Hospital - McGill University - Report, Progress - Ivan B. Pless, M.D. (81-0756-81), 1983-1985 (Box 101, Folder 1187)
    - Montreal Children's Hospital - McGill University - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - (81-0756-81), 1987 (Box 101, Folder 1188)
    - Montreal Children's Hospital - McGill University - Ivan B. Pless, M.D. (81-0756-81), 1980-1981 (Box 101, Folder 1189)
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Report, Publication/Manuscript - Anne Morris, M.A. (76-0617-76), 1973 (Box 101, Folder 1190)
      See Series 5c, Special Formats (Audiovisual and digital material), reel 15.
    - Mount Sinai School of Medicine - Report, Publication/Manuscript - Carter Marshall, M.D. (76-0617-76), 1976 (Box 101, Folder 1191)
    - National Academy of Sciences National Research Council - Administration - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1970-1984 (Box 101, Folder 1193)
    - National Academy of Sciences National Research Council - Application - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1981 (Box 101, Folder 1194)
    - National Academy of Sciences National Research Council - Bibliography - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), after 1984 (Box 101, Folder 1195)
    - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council - Finance - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1981-1984 (Box 102, Folder 1196)
    - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council - General Correspondence - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1982-1985 (Box 102, Folder 1197)
    - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council - Report, Final - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1984 (Box 102, Folder 1198)
    - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1982 (Box 102, Folder 1199)
    - National Academy of Sciences, National Research Council - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - David Goslin, Ph.D.; Alfred Kahn, Ph.D. (81-0785-81), 1981-1983 (Box 102, Folder 1200)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - Administration - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1980-1981 (Box 102, Folder 1201)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - Application - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1202)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - Finance - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1980-1984 (Box 102, Folder 1203)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - General Correspondence - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1980-1988 (Box 102, Folder 1204)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - Report, Progress - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1986-1987 (Box 102, Folder 1205)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - Report, Final - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1985-1987 (Box 102, Folder 1206)
    - National Center for Juvenile Justice - Richard Gable (80-0744-80), 1980 (Box 102, Folder 1207)
    - National Committee for Citizens in Education - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Carl Marburger (79-0669-78), 1981 (Box 103, Folder 1208)
    - National Council on Family Relations - Administration - Ruth Jewson (80-0718-80), 1980 (Box 103, Folder 1209)
    - National Council on Family Relations - Application - Ruth Jewson (80-0718-80), 1980 (Box 103, Folder 1210)
    - National Council on Family Relations - General Correspondence - Ruth Jewson (80-0718-80), 1980-1981 (Box 103, Folder 1211)
    - National Council on Family Relations - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Ruth Jewson (80-0718-80), 1980 (Box 103, Folder 1212)
    - National Dance Institute - Administration - Gigi Ledkovsky (81-0789-81), 1980-1985 (Box 103, Folder 1213)
    - National Dance Institute - Application - Gigi Ledkovsky (81-0789-81), 1981-1985 (Box 103, Folder 1214)
    - National Dance Institute - Finance - Gigi Ledkovsky (81-0789-81), 1981-1982 (Box 103, Folder 1215)
    - National Dance Institute - Report, Final - Gigi Ledkovsky (81-0789-81), 1982 (Box 103, Folder 1216)
    - National Dance Institute - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Henry Epstein, M.D. (72-0421-72), 1976 (Box 103, Folder 1217)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - Administration - Ernest Robles (82-0790-81), 1981-1987 (Box 103, Folder 1218)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - Application - Ernest Robles (85-0790-81), 1981-1985 (Box 103, Folder 1218)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - Finance - Ernest Robles (85-0790-81), 1982-1984 (Box 103, Folder 1219)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - General Correspondence - Ernest Robles (85-0790-81), 1984 (Box 103, Folder 1220)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - Report, Final - Ernest Robles (85-0790-81), 1984-1987 (Box 103, Folder 1221)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - Report, Progress - Ernest Robles (85-0790-81), 1983-1987 (Box 103, Folder 1222)
    - National Hispanic Scholarship Fund - Report, Progress - Ernest Robles (85-0790-81), 1983-1987 (Box 103, Folder 1222)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Administration - Leon Johnson (81-0279-70), 1971-1981 (Box 104, Folder 1223)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Application - Leon Johnson (81-0279-70), 1971-1986 (Box 104, Folder 1224)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Finance - Leon Johnson (81-0279-70), 1973-1982 (Box 104, Folder 1225)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Report, Final - Leon Johnson (81-0279-70), 1982 (Box 104, Folder 1226)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Report, Progress - Leon Johnson (81-0279-70), 1980-1981 (Box 104, Folder 1227)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Report, Progress - Leon Johnson (81-0279-70), 1971-1981 (Box 104, Folder 1228)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Administration - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1977-1989 (Box 104, Folder 1229)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Application - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1980-1984 (Box 104, Folder 1230)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Finance - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1983-1988 (Box 104, Folder 1231)
    - National Medical Fellowships - General Correspondence - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1982-1987 (Box 104, Folder 1232)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Report, Final - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1987 (Box 104, Folder 1233)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Report, Progress - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1982-1983 (Box 104, Folder 1234)
    - National Medical Fellowships - Leon Johnson (82-0761-81), 1981-1983 (Box 104, Folder 1235)
    - National Opinion Research Center - Report, Final - Robert Michael (86-1065-86), 1988 (Box 104, Folder 1236)
    - National Opinion Research Center - Report, Progress - Robert Michael (86-1065-86), 1986-1988 (Box 104, Folder 1237)
    - National School Volunteer Program - Administration - John Alden (77-0637-76), 1976-1978 (Box 105, Folder 1238)
    - National School Volunteer Program - Application - John Alden (77-0637-76), 1977-1978 (Box 105, Folder 1239)
    - National School Volunteer Program - Bibliography - John Alden (77-0637-76), after 1978 (Box 105, Folder 1240)
    - National School Volunteer Program - Finance - John Alden (77-0637-76), 1979 (Box 105, Folder 1241)
    - National School Volunteer Program - General Correspondence - John Alden (77-0637-76), 1978-1980 (Box 105, Folder 1242)
    - National School Volunteer Program - General Correspondence - John Alden (77-0637-76), 1978-1980 (Box 105, Folder 1243)
    - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Foundation - Administration - Carolyn Szbist (80-0703-79), 1979-1980 (Box 105, Folder 1244)
    - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Foundation - Application - Carolyn Szbist (80-0703-79), 1979 (Box 105, Folder 1245)
    - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Foundation - Finance - Carolyn Szbist (80-0703-79), 1981 (Box 105, Folder 1246)
    - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Foundation - General Correspondence - Carolyn Szbist (80-0703-79), 1980-1982 (Box 105, Folder 1247)
    - National Sudden Infant Death Syndrome Foundation - Report, Final - Carolyn Szbist (80-0703-79), 1981 (Box 105, Folder 1248)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Administration - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1977 (Box 105, Folder 1249)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Application - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1977-1978 (Box 105, Folder 1250)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1980 (Box 105, Folder 1251)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Administration - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1977-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1252)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Application - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1978-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1253)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Finance - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1978-1980 (Box 105, Folder 1254)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - General Correspondence - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1979-1980 (Box 105, Folder 1255)
    - National Youth Work Alliance - Report, Progress - William Treanor (78-0668-77), 1979 (Box 105, Folder 1256)
    - National Science for Youth Foundation - Administration - John Ripley Forbes (75-0553-74), 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1257)
    - National Science for Youth Foundation - Application - John Ripley Forbes (75-0553-74), 1974 (Box 105, Folder 1258)
    - National Science for Youth Foundation - Finance - John Ripley Forbes (75-0553-74), 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 1259)
    - National Science for Youth Foundation - Report, Final - John Ripley Forbes (75-0553-74), 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 1250)
    - Navajo Health Authority - Administration - Philip Longhurst (76-0618-75), 1976-1977 (Box 105, Folder 1251)
    - Navajo Health Authority - Application - Philip Longhurst (76-0618-75), 1975-1976 (Box 105, Folder 1252)
    - Navajo Health Authority - Finance - Philip Longhurst (76-0618-75), 1978-1979 (Box 105, Folder 1253)
    - Navajo Health Authority - General Correspondence - Philip Longhurst (76-0618-75), 1976-1979 (Box 106, Folder 1254)
    - Navajo Health Authority - Report, Final - Philip Longhurst (76-0618-75), 1978 (Box 106, Folder 1255)
    - Navajo Health Authority - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Philip Longhurst (76-0618-75), 1974-1978 (Box 106, Folder 1256)
    - University of Nevada - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Beatrice Gardner, Ph.D.; Allen Gardner, Ph.D. (72-0422-72), 1976-1980 (Box 106, Folder 1257)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Administration - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1975-1980 (Box 106, Folder 1258)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Application - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1973-1981 (Box 106, Folder 1259)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Bibliography - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), after 1981 (Box 106, Folder 1260)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Finance - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1976-1982 (Box 106, Folder 1261)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - General Correspondence - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1974-1978 (Box 106, Folder 1262)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Report, Final - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1980-1982 (Box 106, Folder 1263)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Report, Progress - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1979-1980 (Box 106, Folder 1264)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1975-1980 (Box 106, Folder 1265)
    - New England Medical Center Hospital - Judith Rubenstein, Ph.D. (74-0512-74), 1974-1977 (Box 106, Folder 1266)
    - University of Medicine and Dentistry of New Jersey - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - John Clabby, Ph.D. (0813), 1984, undated (Box 107, Folder 1267)
    - University of New Mexico, School of Medicine - Administration - Irving N. Berlin, M.D. (80-0711-80), 1980 (Box 107, Folder 1268)
    - University of New Mexico, School of Medicine - Application - Irving N. Berlin, M.D. (80-0711-80), 1980 (Box 107, Folder 1269)
    - University of New Mexico, School of Medicine - Finance - Irving N. Berlin, M.D. (80-0711-80), 1981 (Box 107, Folder 1270)
    - University of New Mexico, School of Medicine - General Correspondence - Irving N. Berlin, M.D. (80-0711-80), 1980-1982 (Box 107, Folder 1271)
    - University of New Mexico, School of Medicine - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Irving N. Berlin, M.D. (80-0711-80), 1982 (Box 107, Folder 1272)
    - New York City Mission Society - Administration - Frank Jones (88-0202-68), 1979-1988 (Box 107, Folder 1273)
    - New York City Mission Society - Application - Frank Jones (88-0202-68), 1979-1990 (Box 107, Folder 1274)
    - New York City Mission Society - Finance - Frank Jones (88-0202-68), 1980-1986 (Box 107, Folder 1275)
    - New York City Mission Society - Report, Final - Frank Jones (88-0202-68), 1981-1989 (Box 107, Folder 1276)
      See Series 5a, Special Formats (Scrapbooks and Photographs), box 284, folder 3590-3591.
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Administration - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1973-1976 (Box 107, Folder 1277)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Application - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1973-1977 (Box 108, Folder 1278)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Finance - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1974-1980 (Box 108, Folder 1279)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - General Correspondence - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1974-1978 (Box 108, Folder 1280)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Report, Final - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1980 (Box 108, Folder 1281)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Report, Progress - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1975-1978 (Box 108, Folder 1282)
    - New York Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Ira Glasser (79-0457-73), 1974-1977 (Box 108, Folder 1283)
    - New York State Bar Association - Administration - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1982-1984 (Box 108, Folder 1284)
    - New York State Bar Association - Application - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 1285)
    - New York State Bar Association - Finance - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1984 (Box 108, Folder 1286)
    - New York State Bar Association - General Correspondence - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1981-1984 (Box 108, Folder 1287)
    - New York State Bar Association - Report, Final - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1984-1988 (Box 108, Folder 1288)
    - New York State Bar Association - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1984-1988 (Box 108, Folder 1289)
    - New York State Bar Association - Howard Schwartz (84-0795-81), 1981-1983 (Box 108, Folder 1290)
    - New York Hospital - Cornell Medical Center - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Elaine Heffner; Elizabeth Balliett (73-0423-72), 1976 (Box 109, Folder 1291)
    - New York University Medical Center - Administration - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1971-1982 (Box 109, Folder 1292)
    - New York University Medical Center - Application - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1980-1982 (Box 109, Folder 1293)
    - New York University Medical Center - Bibliography - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), after 1986 (Box 109, Folder 1294)
    - New York University Medical Center - Finance - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1982-1985 (Box 109, Folder 1295)
    - New York University Medical Center - General Correspondence - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1981-1986 (Box 109, Folder 1296)
    - New York University Medical Center - Report, Final - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1980-1986 (Box 109, Folder 1297)
    - New York University Medical Center - Report, Progress - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1982-1983 (Box 109, Folder 1298)
    - New York University Medical Center - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1986-1990 (Box 109, Folder 1299)
    - New York University Medical Center - Wayne Gordon, Ph.D. (81-0751-81), 1980-1986 (Box 109, Folder 1300)
    - New York University Medical Center - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Clark Randt, M.D. (69-0227-69), 1972-1975 (Box 109, Folder 1301)
    - New York University - School of Medicine - Report, Publications/Manuscripts (73-0487-73), 1975-1976 (Box 109, Folder 1302)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Administration - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1981-1983 (Box 109, Folder 1303)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Application - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1980-1984 (Box 109, Folder 1304)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Finance - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1980-1984 (Box 110, Folder 1305)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - General Correspondence - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1982-1983 (Box 110, Folder 1306)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Report, Final - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1984 (Box 110, Folder 1307)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1982-1987 (Box 110, Folder 1,308-1309)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Lewis Margolis, M.D. (81-0778-81), 1981-1989 (Box 110, Folder 1310)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Administration - C. Arden Miller, M.D. (81-0786-81), 1981 (Box 110, Folder 1311)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Application - C. Arden Miller, M.D. (81-0786-81), 1981-1982 (Box 110, Folder 1312)
    - University of North Carolina, Chapel Hill - Finance - C. Arden Miller, M.D. (81-0786-81), 1981-1982 (Box 110, Folder 1313)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Administration - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1978-1979 (Box 110, Folder 1314)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Application - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1977-1979 (Box 110, Folder 1315)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Bibliography - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), after 1978 (Box 110, Folder 1316)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Finance - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1978-1980 (Box 110, Folder 1317)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Report, Final - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1978-1980 (Box 110, Folder 1318)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Report, Progress - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1978 (Box 110, Folder 1319)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Report, Progress - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1978 (Box 110, Folder 1320)
    - University of North Carolina, Greensboro - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Hyman Rodman, Ph.D. (77-0639-77), 1978-1980 (Box 111, Folder 1321)
    - North Shore University Hospital, Cornell University Medical College - Administration - Rita Harper, M.D.; Daniel Stern, M.D. (78-0671-78), 1978 (Box 111, Folder 1322)
    - North Shore University Hospital, Cornell University Medical College - Application - Rita Harper, M.D.; Daniel Stern, M.D. (78-0671-78), 1978-1983 (Box 111, Folder 1323)
    - North Shore University Hospital, Cornell University Medical College - Rita Harper, M.D.; Daniel Stern, M.D. (78-0671-78), 1978 (Box 111, Folder 1324)
    - Northeastern University - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Harlan Lane, Ph.D. (76-0619-76), 1978 (Box 111, Folder 1325)
    - Ohio State University - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Hoyt Sherman, Ph.D. (48-0027-48), 1948-1949 (Box 111, Folder 1326-1328)
    - Ohio State University - Reports, Publications/Manuscripts - Hoyt Sherman, Ph.D. (48-0027-48), 1950-1952 (Box 111, Folder 1329-1330)
    - Oregon Research Institute - Report, Final - Lita Furby, Ph.D. (74-0424-72), 1974 (Box 112, Folder 1331-1332)
    - Oregon Research Institute - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Lita Furby, Ph.D. (74-0424-72), 1974 (Box 113, Folder 1333-1336)
    - Oregon Research Institute - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Lita Furby, Ph.D. (74-0424-72), 1978-1980 (Box 113, Folder 1337)
    - University of Oslo - Report, Publication (54-0019-47), 1954 (Box 114, Folder 1338)
    - Palo Alto Medical Research Foundation - Administration - Gurdon Pulford, M.D.; Dean Coddington, M.D. (80-0719-80), 1980-1982 (Box 114, Folder 1339)
    - Palo Alto Medical Research Foundation - Application - Gurdon Pulford, M.D.; Dean Coddington, M.D. (80-0719-80) (Box 114, Folder 1340)
    - Palo Alto Medical Research Foundation - Finance - Gurdon Pulford, M.D.; Dean Coddington, M.D. (80-0719-80), 1982 (Box 114, Folder 1,340b)
    - Palo Alto Medical Research Foundation - Report, Final - Gurdon Pulford, M.D.; Dean Coddington, M.D. (80-0719-80), 1981-1982 (Box 114, Folder 1341)
    - Pan American Health & Education Foundation - Administration - Robert Klein, Ph.D. (78-0425-78), 1977-1979 (Box 114, Folder 1342)
    - Pan American Health & Education Foundation - Application - Robert Klein, Ph.D. (78-0425-78), 1978 (Box 114, Folder 1343)
    - Pan American Health & Education Foundation - Finance - Robert Klein, Ph.D. (78-0425-78), 1980 (Box 114, Folder 1344)
    - Pan American Health & Education Foundation - General Correspondence - Robert Klein, Ph.D. (78-0425-78), 1979-1981 (Box 114, Folder 1345)
    - Pan American Health & Education Foundation - Report, Final - Robert Klein, Ph.D. (78-0425-78), 1982 (Box 114, Folder 1346)
    - Pan American Health & Education Foundation - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Robert Klein, Ph.D. (78-0425-78), 1977 (Box 114, Folder 1347)
    - Parents' and Children's Services of Children's Mission Project for the Study of Child Abuse - Report, Publications/Manuscripts (71-0283-71), 1972 (Box 114, Folder 1348)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Carroll Rosenberg, Ph.D. (70-0230-70), 1972-1974 (Box 114, Folder 1349-1350)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Eliot Stellar, Ph.D. (79-0672-79), 1982 (Box 114, Folder 1351)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Administration - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1980-1984 (Box 114, Folder 1352)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Application - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1980-1986 (Box 114, Folder 1353)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Bibliography - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1986 (Box 114, Folder 1354)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Finance - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1981-1984 (Box 114, Folder 1355)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Report, Final - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1981-1985 (Box 114, Folder 1356)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1980-1984, undated (Box 114, Folder 1357-1358)
    - University of Pennsylvania - Karl Rickels, M.D. (83-0727-80), 1980-1983 (Box 114, Folder 1359)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Administration - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1978-1984 (Box 114, Folder 1360)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Application - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1978-1981 (Box 115, Folder 1361)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Finance - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1982-1985 (Box 115, Folder 1362)
    - Pennsylvania State University - General Correspondence - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1981-1985 (Box 115, Folder 1363)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Report, Progress - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1983-1985 (Box 115, Folder 1364)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Report, Publications/Manuscripts - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1985 (Box 115, Folder 1365)
    - Pennsylvania State University - Dorris Tinker, Ph.D. (82-0673-79), 1978-1981 (Box 115, Folder 1366)